{
   "QA":[
      {
        "QID":"p1u1-b1",
        "type":"Spelling",
        "question":"Classmate",
        "correctAnswer":"Classmate"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u1-b2",
        "type":"Spelling",
        "question":"Goodbye",
        "correctAnswer":"Goodbye"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u1-b5",
        "type":"Spelling",
        "question":"Greet",
        "correctAnswer":"Greet"
      },
      {
         "QID":"p1u1-b6",
         "type":"Spelling",
         "question":"Hello",
         "correctAnswer":"Hello"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u1-b7",
        "type":"Spelling",
        "question":"Monitor",
        "correctAnswer":"Monitor"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u1-b8",
        "type":"Spelling",
        "question":"Teacher",
        "correctAnswer":"Teacher"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u1-b9",
        "type":"Spelling",
        "question":"Friend",
        "correctAnswer":"Friend"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u1-b10",
        "type":"Spelling",
        "question":"Gardener",
        "correctAnswer":"Gardener"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u1-b11",
        "type":"Spelling",
        "question":"Driver",
        "correctAnswer":"Driver"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u1-b12",
        "type":"Spelling",
        "question":"Coach",
        "correctAnswer":"Coach"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u1-b13",
        "type":"Spelling",
        "question":"Leader",
        "correctAnswer":"Leader"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u2-a1",
        "type":"Spelling",
        "question":"Family",
        "correctAnswer":"Family"
      },
      {
         "QID":"p1u2-a2",
         "type":"Spelling",
         "question":"Sister",
         "correctAnswer":"Sister"
      },
      {
         "QID":"p1u2-a3",
         "type":"Spelling",
         "question":"Father",
         "correctAnswer":"Father"
      },
      {
         "QID":"p1u2-a4",
         "type":"Spelling",
         "question":"Mother",
         "correctAnswer":"Mother"
      },
      {
         "QID":"p1u2-a5",
         "type":"Spelling",
         "question":"Brother",
         "correctAnswer":"Brother"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u2-a6",
        "type":"Spelling",
        "question":"Grandmother",
        "correctAnswer":"Grandmother"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u2-a7",
        "type":"Spelling",
        "question":"Grandfather",
        "correctAnswer":"Grandfather"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u2-a8",
        "type":"Spelling",
        "question":"Parents",
        "correctAnswer":"Parents"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u2-a9",
        "type":"Spelling",
        "question":"Children",
        "correctAnswer":"Children"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u3-a2",
        "type":"Listening",
        "question":"Book",
        "correctAnswer":"Book"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u3-a3",
        "type":"Listening",
        "question":"Pen",
        "correctAnswer":"Pen"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u3-a4",
        "type":"Listening",
        "question":"Eraser",
        "correctAnswer":"Eraser"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u3-a5",
        "type":"Listening",
        "question":"Pencil",
        "correctAnswer":"Pencil"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u3-a6",
        "type":"Listening",
        "question":"Case",
        "correctAnswer":"Case"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u3-a7",
        "type":"Listening",
        "question":"Ruler",
        "correctAnswer":"Ruler"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u3-a8",
        "type":"Listening",
        "question":"Crayons",
        "correctAnswer":"Crayons"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u3-a9",
        "type":"Listening",
        "question":"Glue",
        "correctAnswer":"Glue"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p1u3-a10",
        "type":"Listening",
        "question":"Stapler",
        "correctAnswer":"Stapler"
      },
      {
        "QID":"p3u1-e1",
        "type":"MultipleChoice",
        "question":"What is the color of apple?",
        "answers":[
           "red",
           "blue",
           "purple",
           "black"
        ],
        "correctAnswer":"red"
     },
     {
       "QID": "p3u1-e2",
       "type":"MultipleChoice",
       "question": "What is the color of banana?",
       "answers": [
         "red",
         "yellow",
         "purple",
         "black"
       ],
       "correctAnswer": "yellow"
     },
     {
      "QID":"p3u2-c1",
      "type":"Listening",
      "question":"general",
      "correctAnswer":"general"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c2",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"maths",
          "correctAnswer":"maths"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c3",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"english",
          "correctAnswer":"english"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c4",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"physical",
          "correctAnswer":"physical"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c5",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"science",
          "correctAnswer":"science"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c6",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"history",
          "correctAnswer":"history"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c7",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"arts",
          "correctAnswer":"arts"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c8",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"geography",
          "correctAnswer":"geography"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c9",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"computer",
          "correctAnswer":"computer"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c10",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"music",
          "correctAnswer":"music"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c11",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"religious",
          "correctAnswer":"religious"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c12",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"project",
          "correctAnswer":"project"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c13",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"dictate",
          "correctAnswer":"dictate"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c14",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"visual",
          "correctAnswer":"visual"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c15",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"internet",
          "correctAnswer":"internet"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c16",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"outing",
          "correctAnswer":"outing"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c17",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"attention",
          "correctAnswer":"attention"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c18",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"listen",
          "correctAnswer":"listen"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c19",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"learn",
          "correctAnswer":"learn"
      },
      {
          "QID":"p3u2-c20",
          "type":"Listening",
          "question":"improve",
          "correctAnswer":"improve"
      }
   ]
}
